powergridindia.com 2016-06-04

# Welcome To PowerGrid

​As a general rule, this website does not collect Personal Information about user who visits the site. Any person can generally visit the site without revealing Personal Information, unless he / she choose to provide such information.

### Site Visit Data

This website records user visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes:

  1. IP address from which user accesses the website;
  2. The type of browser and operating system used to access the website;
  3. The date and time user accessed the website;
  4. The pages user has accessed and the documents download;
  5. If user reaches this website from another website, the address of that referring website.

This information is used only to help POWERGRID make the website more user-friendly. POWERGRID never tracks or records information about individuals and their visits. POWERGRID makes no attempt to link this information with the identity of individuals visiting the website unless an attempt to damage the site has been detected.

POWERGRID does not identify users or their browsing activities, except when a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the server provider’s logs.

###  Cookies

A cookie is a piece of software code that an internet web site sends to user’s browser when he /she accesses information at that site. This website uses cookies but not for user information gathering.

### Email Management

 User’s email address is recorded only if user chooses to send a message. It will only be used for the purpose for which user provides it and will not be added to a mailing list. User’s email address will not be used for any other purpose unless it is intended by the user, and will not be disclosed, without user’s consent.

### Collection of Personal Information

If users are asked for any other personal information user will be informed how it will be used. If at any time user believes the principles referred to in this privacy statement have not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, he/she can notify the webmaster through the contact us page.
